Think fast.
All right. You good?
All good. See you. Good luck, Coach.
Gabby!
Aah!
It's our last first day of free education,
and I wanna cry.
Please don't.
Ooh-hoo, what's this, now?
New record, folks...
your girl is dancing at... 7:28 a.m.
I'm just celebrating
our last first day of free education.
Did you take an Adderall?
Mm-mm. This is all naturel, baby.
Ugh, what's his deal?
So obnoxious.
Okay, let's go.
I'm so glad we're at the
same school this year.
McKenna?
McKenna...?
All right. Gabriella?
Here!
I have ten texts, four DMs,
and an email from Emily.
Pray for me.
You're not alone.
She's blowing up the cheer group chat.
Is this gonna be an all-season thing?
Why did you make me join?
Drayton?
Drayton Lahey?
Mr. Lahey?
Present.
Starting the year off
with a low bar, Mr. Lahey.
Nah, I'm just managing expectations.
There's only one way to go from here.
All right, let's go to our seats, shall we?
Let's discuss the summer reading.
Dallas, thank you.
Kick us off.
Yes. Yes, well...
I thought that the...
that the book we read...
Romeo and Juliet.
Romeo and Juliet, was... interesting.
"Interesting."
Please...
be specific.
The ending was tragic.
Because Romeo and Juliet
had their whole lives ahead of them,
but instead, they threw it all away
for some meaningless hook-up at a party.
So...
yeah...
tragic.
Anyone care to counter?
I don't know.
Maybe they just wanted
to have a little fun.
Is that so bad?
They died.
Okay, let's open
our copies to Act V, Scene III.
Okay.
How you feelin', Coach?
Excited?
Yeah.
Feeling good. Feeling strong.
Uh... to what do I owe the pleasure?
Um...
Listen.
I noticed you've eased up on practice
a little bit this week.
Are you sure now's the time
you wanna scale back on their conditioning?
Mr. Lahey, we just
wrapped up on two-a-days,
so the team's already got their legs back.
I just want to make sure
Drayton gets as much time as possible
with those receivers.
If I overwork him too much
through the pre-season,
we run the risk of injury.
Of course. Of course.
I just, uh...
as you know...
Drayton's committed to Waco,
uh, but there's a very real possibility
he could be starting quarterback there.
Now, I-I don't need to tell you how huge
of an opportunity that is,
and we need to do everything we can
to keep him focused, on track,
free of distractions.
You got it.
Thanks, Coach.
Point your toes!
Stronger arms!
Whoo, let's go!
And hit!
Geez, it's practice, not the Super Bowl.
Funny. All right, line it up, ladies.
Time to review "Go, fight, win."
Go! Fight! Win!
Okay, go!
I got it! I got it!
All right, all right, boys,
up-downs followed by wind sprints.
Coach, uh, practice is over,
according to your schedule.
I know my schedule.
So does your dad, apparently.
What? What'd he say?
Hey, don't worry about it.
We'll talk about it later.
Now, go join your team, Captain.
Sure you don't wanna find your birth dad?
Maybe he'll adopt me two for one.
Your dad means well. He's just...
A prick.
Difficult.
But you can't let him get in your head.
I don't.
Oh, he's there. Rent-free.
Yo, Chase! Go long!
Yo, girls!
Damn.
Nice catch, Cheer!
Not my name, Quarterback!
Who is that?
Gabby?
She's head cheerleader, class president.
I heard she just broke
up with her boyfriend.
We all know Gabby.
I mean that one, the new cheerleader.
She's in my English class.
Dallas Bryan.
She just transferred here.
I think she's a dancer, theater kid.
Bryan, as in...?
New coach's sister.
Totally off limits.
That explains the cannon.
Hut! Go!
Go! Quick feet!
Bring it in!
Bring it in.
Take a knee. Take a knee.
All right.
Good job today, team.
Get your rest,
'cause we're back at it again tomorrow.
Wolves on three! Wolves on me!
One! Two! Three...
Wolves!
Drayton. My office.
A lot of D1 schools have
reached out about you.
I know that you're...
verbally committed to Waco,
but I wanted to let you
know that you got options.
Wow...
"options."
Thanks, Andy Reid.
Drayton.
Look, you got a serious shot at going pro.
You're talented,
but you need an attitude adjustment.
I'm a quadruple legacy at Waco.
There are no options.
My dad's already booked my flight in May
for summer conditioning, so...
But is that what you want?
Uh...
I don't know. Never thought about it.
We got some time.
Just keep your head down,
show up, and do the work...
and think about it.
Whatever you say.
Look. I get it.
I was the star quarterback too.
The pressure can be...
overwhelming in this town.
So if you ever need to talk...
my door's always open.
Sure.
Hey, Cheer. Sorry about earlier.
My aim's usually spot-on.
I'll take your word for it, Quarterback.
You don't have to. You can ask around.
I'm pretty much a football legend.
Wow. Yeah. Your modesty is so refreshing.
It's his most admirable quality.
I was just apologizing to Dallas
for, uh, almost taking
her head off at practice.
And I was just explaining to Drayton
that I can defend myself.
Yo, Dray! Go long!
Longer, dude! Come on!
Careful! That's my...
Ooh, dang!
Car!
Crap, I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
It'll be okay. Let's take it to the shop,
and I'll see if my mom
can pick us up from there?
I could follow you and
give y'all a ride back,
make up for my clumsy brother.
Thank you. That's really sweet.
Could you give me a ride
to my studio instead?
I got you.
Okay, let's go.
You should be more careful, bro.
Shut up, Chase.
Extend... pow!
Nice!
Now, three, and two, three, four,
five, six...
Energy, come on!
Two...
Looking good!
I've been working on
my audition all summer.
Nathan's gonna record me, Gabby'll edit,
and this time next year,
I will never have to mop the sweat
off a ballet floor again.
Won't be the same without you.
You know, the dean at Summit
Dance Conservatory and I
go way back.
I could call him up, put in a good word?
Might be nice to have a backup plan.
CalArts is the only plan.
You sound just like your mama.
I just want you to have options.
CalArts is an incredible program,
but it's extremely competitive.
Which is why I've been training for years.
I literally just danced
circles around everyone else.
You're an incredible dancer...
but you're not ready.
Not yet.
The bar at CalArts is nearly impossible,
especially for video auditions.
But not out of the realm of possibility.
Now you really sound like your mama.
You really wanna do this?
I do!
Then you need to get out of your head.
I can see you thinking about the choreo.
You're too rigid.
You need to be spontaneous.
But it's a routine. We follow the steps.
But it has to feel like
it's the first and last
time that you'll ever do it.
You'll get there.
You'll lock up?
Hey! It was my turn to do the shopping.
Yeah, but I was on my
way back from practice,
figured I'd bang it out. One
less thing on your plate.
Mm. What a sweet legal guardian.
You can just say "brother."
Okay.
Ooh! Are you making fried rice this week?
Of course.
When are you gonna teach me how to make it?
When you are ready, young Padawan.
Mm.
How was your day?
Awful.
Besides the car,
Alicia said I'm never getting into CalArts,
and I should quit while I'm ahead.
What did she actually say?
That I'm not ready, but I'll get there.
Mm. That sounds about right.
But...
now I have to throw out my whole routine
and start from scratch,
and it'll be hours on
top of school and work,
and Gabby convinced me
to join cheerleading.
Didn't CalArts say that you need...
Extracurriculars, I know.
So I need to put my head down and focus.
Look, I hear you,
but in the meantime,
you're letting your senior year pass you by
before it's even started.
Maybe joining cheer, or going to a party,
or dare I say a date?
I don't date. -Even
though you don't date.
You know?
Actually enjoy being 18.
That doesn't sound so bad.
You know, you're not half bad
at this inspiring the youths thing.
Thank you.
What else we got in here?
Hey, Cheer.
Here to break my front window too?
I'm sorry about earlier.
This... should more than cover it.
I'm not your charity case.
Look, it's not like that. All right?
It was my fault, and I
want to make it right.
Okay. Thank you.
I'll get you back.
No way. Consider it my idiot tax.
In that case, I think you're short.
Guess I'll see you at school?
Mr. Douglas agreed to write
my letter of recommendation for Princeton.
Yes, Gabs! That's huge.
Thank you. I'm so excited. I really feel...
Hey, guys. Dallas, how's your car?
In the ICU, having open-heart surgery,
but thanks for asking.
Your presentation
on the radioactive nature of bananas
was fascinating, but...
also terrifying.
Thank you.
Don't worry. You'd have
to eat a million bananas
to actually die of radiation poisoning.
When you're valedictorian,
you're gonna crush your speech.
Thank you. That's... very sweet.
Dallas, come sit with us.
Wow. Cheer's joining us.
Wow. Must be your lucky day, Quarterback.
So, you coming to the party tonight?
Not really my scene.
Well, if you change your mind,
be happy to give you a ride.
Unless, uh... boyfriend's the jealous type?
I don't have a jealous boyfriend,
super-toxic,
I don't date.
Not yet...
but every rule has exceptions.
Not this one.
No, I'm outta here the
day after graduation,
so there's no point.
I guess.
But, what, you don't ever have an itch
that needs to be scratched?
Thanks for your concern,
but I manage just fine.
I don't know why
everyone's so obsessed with him.
He's not as charming as he thinks he is.
I don't know.
I sensed a vibe.
Ugh!
He is so smug! And cocky.
And he's hooked up with half of our squad.
Did you see his hickeys?
Plural.
Wow! Slut-shaming?
That's a little off-brand.
Just an observation.
But... come on!
Like, a jock who's never had a girlfriend?
So cliché.
Girl, you're so into him!
It's literally obvious to everyone but you.
Ugh.
Fine.
Maybe you really do hate him,
but what if some other great,
equally-hot guy came around?
Would you give him a chance?
No! Because I'm doing just fine on my own,
and I don't have time for...
Dallas, it's our last year.
I'm in five APs, two clubs,
and I said yes
when Josh invited me to the party tonight.
Hmm!
It's almost like it's less about timing
and more about not letting your guard down.
Ouch.
I'm sorry.
But it's my job as your
bestie to be honest with you,
even when it's hard,
because I love you.
I love you too.
What?
I couldn't hear that.
Fine!
I love you too.
So you'll come to the party with me?
Please? Please, please, please.
I have no problem admitting
I'm crushing hard on Josh,
and I need my wing-woman.
Fine.
Thank you! Thank you!
Can't wait to return the favor.
Drayton or otherwise.
Five, six, seven, eight...
I need more emotion.
Stop.
I'm not feeling it.
And neither are you.
Okay. Well, what does that mean?
It means
that you're still thinking too much.
Stop holding yourself back.
Let yourself go!
It's getting late.
You can keep going, but
just lock up afterward.
Actually, I... I have plans tonight.
Okay! I love that for you.
Oh! The whole senior class is here.
I'm gonna find Josh.
I'm gonna go find a corner to sit in.
No!
If you're gonna wing-woman
me, I need you close.
What if I misread all the signals
and he was just, like, being nice?
Oh, stop!
He looks at you
the way that Nathan looks
at Domino's cheesy bread.
See?
You look... beautiful.
Thanks.
The space buns took a lot
longer than I expected.
Okay, well, my work is done.
If you need me, I will be anywhere else.
Cheer.
You're, like... obsessed with me.
Mm. Yeah, you'd certainly like to think so.
I'm just trying to give Romeo
and Juliet some privacy.
Hopefully it's more than a...
how did you put it?
A meaningless hookup at a party?
Wow. Now who's obsessed with who?
Thank you.
I'm surprised you're here.
Doesn't seem like your vibe.
It's not.
Neither is this town.
It's so suffocating.
Everyone else seems happy.
Ever think maybe it's you?
I can't tell if you actually mean that,
or you're trying to neg me.
Which version gets me a date?
None.
Just 'cause you're hot
doesn't mean everyone wants to date you.
So you think I'm hot?
No.
I mean, yes, like,
objectively speaking, then...
Ugh, you're so smug. It's infuriating.
Chill, Cheer. You're hot too.
I know.
Yo, Drayton!
Ready for some beer pong?
Rematch for last week?
Aw, man, I'm out. Practice tomorrow.
Respect, man.
You could play with water.
You wanna play?
You realize I'm undefeated.
Are you scared I'm gonna take your title?
Ha!
You wish.
Care to make it interesting?
I'm listening.
If I win,
I get to take you on that date.
But if I lose...
I'll never ask again.
Come on.
You know, you can forfeit now
and let me take you to dinner.
Are you always this entitled?
How 'bout Italian?
Yo, dude.
I thought you weren't playing, man.
I'm not. I'm hydrating.
Oh! Yo!
No way.
Goodbye, Drayton.
Yo!
I mean, she totally kicked your ass, man.
Uh-uh-uh.
Cut your losses, Quarterback.
Best two out of three.
Oh, I know you're used
to getting what you want,
but you lost fair and square.
Sorry, not sorry.
You're really doubling down.
You know, it kinda makes me think
you know just how much fun we could have.
I don't know what kind of
games you're trying to play,
but I'm out.
Dray, babe, I was
hoping I'd see you here.
Want to grab a beer? Maybe go for a swim?
Like last time.
Did you remember your bathing suit?
What's the fun in that?
Hit me.
Dallas!
Hey. Josh asked me to grab a bite.
Are you okay to get home,
and would you be pissed if I went?
I would be pissed
if you didn't go.
Don't worry, I'll catch a lift,
but I expect a full report tomorrow.
Thank you!
I'll tell you everything.
Okay.
I love you. Bye.
Cheers.
Ugh. Man, you're not messing around.
Nope. Night, Chase.
Goodnight.
Night.
Oh, crap. Still no service.
I hate this town.
Nope.
I love walking. More steps.
Jesus, Drayton!
I thought I was about to
be violently murdered.
Are you insane?
Didn't your parents ever tell you
not to walk alone at night?
Get on. I'll give you a ride.
Yeah, I would rather walk 15,000 miles
than get on your bike.
Your house is the other way.
Oh, shit. I'm drunk.
You don't say.
Oh, no! Nathan can't see me like this.
The Earth is spinning.
Here.
Have you ever ridden a bike before?
No.
Well, I'm honored to be your first.
You live here?
Home, sweet home.
Hmph.
Guess you do always get what do you want.
Is this what you want?
No.
Maybe. I don't know.
Look, I can take you back to Gabby's,
but I'm pretty sure I saw her
and Josh leave together, so.
Yeah.
It's nice that they're so into each other.
It almost makes me wish that I was...
It's okay.
Let's get you inside.
Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, you think you're so smooth,
with your motorcycle and your smile,
and your shirtlessness.
I bet this was just all a giant scheme
to get me into bed and to...
So it wasn't a giant scheme?
Excuse me?
Because I'm a jock,
I don't understand consent?
Mm. Maybe you're not so cliché.
Good night.
Make me more upset,
that you blew off the dinner,
or that you forgot about it.
No excuse. I went out.
That's what you do in high school.
And you blew off a dinner
that I arranged months ago,
that we've been prepping for for weeks?
It was one dinner.
It was an alumni dinner
with the head coach of Waco!
What is the matter with you?
Any idea how humiliated I was?
I'll add it to the list.
Excuse me?
Nothing. I ju...
I wanted to go to a party. Is that so bad?
You will have plenty of time for parties,
but right now, you need to buckle down
and get your head in the game.
I'll go distract them
so you can sneak out.
Okay, okay. Thank you. Um...
I'm so... I'm so sorry to, um...
well, we didn't...
I'm... I'm gonna... we...
I'm gonna go. Ahem.
You're in season. All right? Act like it.
Honey, I think you made your point.
It's not gonna happen again, right?
Right.
All right. Get dressed. I'll
drop you off at the gym.
What about Josh?
He's already there.
You know you can tell
me whenever you're ready.
Gabby, for the last time,
nothing happened with Drayton, I swear.
And you still haven't talked
to him since last week?
I've been avoiding him,
and it seems like he's
back in football mode.
I don't wanna talk about it.
Well, these college apps are killing me.
They should rename it
"collegiate trauma dumping."
I know. It's, like, do I
write about being broke,
or my dead parents?
Or the fact that the Earth is slowly dying,
so nothing really matters?
I think they want dead parents.
I know! And that's exactly
why I've been avoiding it.
Hey, wait.
What are you wearing to the away game?
Our "Saucy Sapphire" uniform?
Obviously. But I mean, like,
for the rest of the trip.
Are there parties, or post-games, or...
you know.
Hmm?
Any chance of hanging
out with a certain QB?
I am not dignifying that with an answer.
Did I mention I saw Drayton yesterday,
when I was with Josh?
Y'all are pretty serious, huh?
Yeah.
I think he's gonna ask me to
be his girlfriend this weekend.
Oh! Oh, my god. Are you gonna hard launch?
Shut up! But yes.
Anyways, Drayton was asking about you.
He only wants what he can't have.
Well... then bring this.
You can really make him suffer.
Just in case.
Aah!
How did you find that?
Just bring it!
All right, wheels up in ten! Chip-chop!
We're burning daylight!
All right! Listen up! Listen up!
Although we're leaving school,
all school rules still apply,
so let's behave like it.
Go, Wolves!
Hey.
Uh, so tonight, there's
some coaches from Waco
coming to watch how
you've been progressing.
Yeah, my dad mentioned that.
Mmhmm.
I hope you don't mind,
but, uh, I took the liberty
to make a couple calls
to get some other folks excited...
Alabama, USC,
UCLA, and Notre Dame.
You didn't have to do that.
I know.
But no pressure.
Just play like you always do,
and you'll have lots of options.
Thanks, Coach. Means a lot.
Sorry, Dallas, can I steal
your seat for a second?
Gabby and I just have to strategize.
Em, we've gone over everything.
Yeah, but we haven't confirmed
our face-paint design.
Or our ponytail height.
Why am I the only one putting
fires out around here?
Okay.
Okay. Yep.
Thank you. Sorry.
Yep.
Come here.
Okay.
Hey, it's me or Chase. All right?
And he's a manspreader. No offense, dude.
No offense taken, man.
I'm surprised your seat's empty.
I was saving it for you.
Grape?
No thanks.
Come on, it's brain food.
You need nutrients.
I win.
Nice catch.
I'm not just good with my hands.
Are you ready-ready?
And we hit the field like...
Ooh!
All night like...
Offense like!
Ooh!
Defense like!
And it sound like...
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
Bring it there.
18, hut!
Yes!
Whoo!
Josh played so well tonight.
I know I'm being biased,
but he definitely set Drayton up
multiple times.
He really did crush it.
They all did.
My cheers were only half fake.
You can't wear that.
Yes, I can, because I'm not going.
Oh, not this again.
I'm stressed about my audition.
I've been slacking,
and, no offense, but it's a little bigger
than some stupid football after-party.
You know, for the players getting scouted,
this game might've earned
them a full ride to college.
Drayton included.
So this stupid after-party
may not be worth celebrating to you,
but it is for some.
I'm gonna go.
You do you.
Ooh... come on.
Please don't do this.
The one in the lobby's working.
And it has better options.
Post-game munchies?
For the party in Chase's room.
It's very loud, very crowded,
and everyone is very drunk.
Aw, darn. I'm so sad to miss it.
Did I mention it was 90 degrees?
Which one do you want?
Those cheesy things.
On me.
And they say chivalry is dead.
So...
if you're not going to
Chase's, what are you doing?
I was trying to work on my solo,
but I'm feeling stuck.
Why?
I-I don't know.
My... my dance teacher,
she said some stuff, and it got in my head.
It's fine.
Um, you should get back to your party.
It's not my party.
But isn't it?
You know, actually...
I was thinking of doing something else.
Wanna join?
Okay. But let me change.
All the coaches
came up to me after.
All of them?
All five schools are interested?
Th-that's amazing.
Yeah, I know, it's pretty cool.
Um... doesn't really matter.
Waco's the plan.
Why Waco?
It's a great school.
Yeah, but so is Notre Dame.
Yeah, but my dad, and his dad,
and his dad's dad,
and his dad's dad's dad
all went to Waco, so...
that's the plan, I guess.
Plans can change.
Where... where are we going?
I can't get into any trouble.
Nathan will kill me.
Relax! I got us. Come on.
Come on.
Hey. Come on.
Dray.
Vinny.
Long time, no see.
Who's this?
Dallas. She's cool. Uh,
we just wanna hang out.
Okay. Only because it's you.
I got it. Thank you.
I, uh, I volunteer at a
sports camp every summer.
I've known Vinny since his
niece started coming years ago,
so he always hooks it up.
So, what do you think?
I know it's not exactly
the kind of dance you do,
but I figured... it couldn't hurt.
Sorry. Was this a dumb idea?
This is awesome!
Come on!
Okay, no, no, no, no, no.
This is salsa!
It's all about the hips.
I definitely don't know
how to move my hips.
Move to the beat.
Okay, no.
Sorry.
Follow my rhythm.
Okay.
Oh... okay.
You're gonna follow my feet.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Three...
Two... nice.
Is this better?
I'm gonna need lessons
if I'm ever gonna keep up with you.
Oh... so you wanna go dancing again?
As friends, of course.
Name a time, and I'm there.
I think maybe I had
the wrong impression of you earlier.
What, that I was a brainless,
man-whoring quarterback?
Well, don't forget egomaniac.
And, uh...
what's your impression now?
That you...
That I...?
Might not be so bad.
Where the hell were you?
Nate...
I don't want to hear it.
I expected this much from
him, but not from you.
Hey, it wasn't her fault.
You're lucky I don't bench you next week
for breaking the rules.
Okay, let's all take a breath.
It's late.
We were very worried
and had to contact Principal Cantor,
so we'll deal with all
this on Monday. Yeah?
Go to your room.
Both of you.
Dallas...
This is a serious infraction,
and it's extremely disappointing.
Drayton, I've gone easy on you in the past,
given your talent and
your family's history,
but this time, I can't look the other way.
Sneaking out on a school trip?
Fraternizing?
Entering a 21-plus establishment?
These aren't small potatoes.
Great. Now I'm craving fries.
Drayton.
Look, I can only speak for myself.
This was uncharacteristic at best,
reckless at worst.
I'm so sorry, and I am...
I'm ashamed of our actions.
You're both suspended for a week.
What?
No! That'll be on my record,
and CalArts will see it.
Please! Can't I do community service?
Or-or wash the graffiti off lockers?
You both violated the rules...
But, Principal Cantor...
and actions have consequences.
Dallas, hold up!
Drayton Francis Lahey!
Get in the car. Now.
I just wanna talk to her.
Absolutely not.
I obviously can't trust you.
The two of you are not
to see each other again.
Waco coaches are coming to
games you won't be playing in.
What were you thinking?
I was...
No, you weren't.
You're too busy throwing
away your entire future
for one night of fun.
It's time to grow up.
I picked up some shifts this week...
and, um, I'm finally gonna take
that donation box to Goodwill.
Thanks.
Nate, I'm sorry for sneaking out
and getting suspended.
I'm keeping my head down until my audition.
I promise it will not happen again.
Just please stop this silent treatment.
I think I overreacted.
I mean, you've never
been in trouble before,
and I told you I wanted you
to act like a normal teenager.
So careful what you ask for, I guess.
So you're not mad anymore?
No, I'm not mad.
I never was mad.
I was just... disappointed.
That's worse!
Look, as a coach,
I'm losing my quarterback
for a week, in season,
and I look incompetent to my boss.
And as my brother?
I was terrified something happened.
I thought that we were closer than that.
We are.
I should've texted you.
At the very least.
Yeah.
Look... when Mom and Dad died,
I didn't hesitate to drop out of Oregon,
and I would do it again
in a heartbeat, because...
we're all that we got, kid.
We gotta protect each other.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I forgive you.
You know, Han Solo...
always used to call Luke "kid."
They were, like, the same age.
Are you trying to tell me
you're not a kid anymore?
By law, I'm an adult, you know. Yeah.
Wow.
If Mom and Dad could see you now...
I miss 'em every day.
Me too.
Aw...
you're muscling through it,
and you're losing your balance.
The tension is showing
all over your dang face.
It's hard.
Life's hard, honey.
What are you doing here?
Look, there's only so many
video games one man can play...
and I wanted to apologize.
You should go.
No, you should stay.
Come here. I think you can
help me with something.
Okay.
Face each other.
Come on, y'all! I don't have all day.
Okay.
You're gonna have a
conversation with your bodies.
No talking.
Let your feelings trigger the movement.
Look, I'm not a dancer.
Everyone's a dancer.
Only move when you feel something.
Surrender. Just let go.
That's it.
Find that connection.
Stay open.
Go with the flow.
Ahem!
Were you anticipating?
No.
Exactly.
You were just going with the flow.
Look, I'm sorry for...
I have nothing to say to you.
I'll do anything to make it up to you.
Please?
You missed a spot.
I never thought he'd suspend us.
That's not...
And I know that's not the point.
I was embarrassed.
But I should've stood up for you,
or at least, not made it worse.
It was shitty.
It was really shitty,
and now my audition is gonna
have to be ten times better
for CalArts to overlook a
suspension on my record.
Look, I'm in the same
boat with Waco and scouts.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I know I also chose to sneak out.
It wasn't all you.
I like Alicia.
Maybe I'll start taking lessons.
You need them.
I didn't think I was that bad.
So... how's your solo going?
Awful.
I only have two months left,
and I'm not even close to ready,
and I have to make the
judges feel my emotion,
which is hard enough in person,
let alone through a video.
You have to audition through video?
Yeah. And it sucks, because
in-person ones are more personal
and you have higher chances of getting in.
That does suck.
Wait, but when you toured the campus,
did you get any face-time
with the dean or anything?
No, I've never seen it.
But I've done my research.
Wait, so this is your dream school,
and you haven't even seen it?
We should go.
I'll book our tickets.
I'm serious! I'll cover it.
Consider it...
idiot tax 2.0.
What about school?
We're suspended. We'll be back by Monday.
You're crazy.
No, I'm not.
Look, you work so hard.
You deserve to see CalArts.
It's literally all you talk about.
It's your dream.
Well...
Good morning, folks.
We'll be landing shortly in Los Angeles,
where it is a sunny 74 degrees.
The studios have sprung floors,
and I can observe a level 402 class...
in 15 minutes.
Are you okay if I go?
Yeah. Uh, I got some things I need to do.
Hot date?
Something like that.
Uh, enjoy your class. We'll meet up later.
Okay. Thank you! Thank you.
Of course.
I'll see you later.
Let's go. Come on.
You know how sometimes you
hype something up so much
that the reality can't
possibly live up to it?
Oh, no.
This is so much better than I imagined it.
Good.
I never thought I'd be
caught dead in an eye mask...
But I get the appeal.
If you show that to anyone...
It is just for me.
Okay.
It's my turn.
Truth or dare?
I welcome the chaos.
Dare.
I dare you to prank-call Josh
and ask if he has any
blow-up dolls for sale.
Okay.
Ahem.
It's ringing.
Mm-hmm.
Hello?
Yes, I'd like to place an
order for a blow-up doll.
My airline lost the luggage.
Uh-huh?
Good call.
I'll try that. Cheers.
Okay, what-what did he say?
A true professional.
Gave me the number to a sex shop.
Oh!
It's your turn. Truth or dare?
Mm. Truth.
Why CalArts?
My mom went to CalArts.
She was such an amazing ballerina.
And I loved watching her dance.
Being here makes me feel close to her.
Close to both my parents.
Was your dad a dancer too?
Oh, God, no.
He had no rhythm,
but he just loved making my mom smile.
Sounds like they were good parents.
They were the best.
And, today, walking around campus,
all the places she used to go...
I feel like she's here.
I'm sorry. I know that sounds crazy.
No, it doesn't.
No, it's okay. I know it does.
No, I... I get it.
You do?
It's my turn.
Dare.
I dare you...
to show me one of the
famous Drayton Lahey moves.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, Dray, babe...
you wanna go skinny-dipping?
Are you jealous?
No.
Curious.
Truth or dare?
Truth.
Do you want me to kiss you?
Yes.
Dray, I think we should get some sleep.
We gotta fly home tomorrow.
Right.
Friends.
Valencia's sunny.
CalArts is incredible.
Everyone was so friendly and talented.
As much as I'd miss you,
I really hope that you get in.
You deserve it.
And... how's Drayton?
No. No, no.
We're-we're just friends.
Really?
It's not worth it.
It's too complicated.
Oh, hey.
I-I gotta go. Love you.
Thanks for the coffee.
It's the least I can do.
Thanks for bringing me here.
Idiot tax 2.0, remember?
So...
what are your plans when we get home?
We should grab a bite.
I really should spend
more time with my brother.
Right. Right.
How 'bout Monday?
Maybe.
After seeing how good the dancers are here,
I-I need to... work on my routine.
Okay, yeah. I guess, uh...
you let me know when you're free.
We'll definitely see each other at games...
bud.
You called him "bud"?
Why not castrate him? It
would've been less painful!
It just came out!
I just can't believe
you two went away and
nothing major happened.
Well, almost.
Oh, my god, I knew it!
Gabby, it was just kissing,
and I wish I could take it back,
because now it's so complicated.
What's complicated?
Literally, what?
You like him, he likes you.
Name one thing that's complicated.
We're graduating soon!
And it's gonna have to end,
like everything inevitably does,
and I'd rather save myself the heartbreak.
Oh, boo... that ship has sailed.
You definitely caught feelings.
No! No. I mean,
do I like spending time with him?
Sure. It's a lot of fun.
And he's really charming, and...
surprisingly very thoughtful.
But I don't... I...
Maybe I like him.
Oh! You more than like him!
Oh, hang on. One sec.
It's Josh.
Hey, babe!
Yes, eight works for dinner later.
Okay, love you too. Bye.
"Love"?
Did you say "love"?
A lot happened while you were away,
and, no shade,
but Josh and I are very
emotionally available.
Gabby, I'm so happy for you.
Oh...
you should try it.
What if he...
You could "what if" forever.
But at some point, you
just have to go for it
and hope for the best.
Oh, hang on.
It's Em.
Hey, girl.
Yeah, I'm studying right
now, but tell me everything.
What? Why are you freaking out, Em?
Of course.
Yes, we are going to practice every day
until the day comes...
yes, until the game. Yes, of course.
Hey.
How's it going?
What'd you want to talk about... bud?
I wish we were back in L.A.
Yeah.
You're being weird.
I'm following your lead.
Hey, well... you shouldn't,
because I'm...
look, I'm a complicated person.
Tell me about it.
You're not exactly a
walk in the park either.
But you kinda like it, don't you?
See? This is what I'm talking about.
And it's making me crazy.
I like spending time with you.
It's annoying,
and cool, and...
I don't know, maybe I...
Maybe what?
Look, I like you.
I think you know that I like you.
But I don't wanna be yanked around.
So either you're in...
or you're out.
I'm in.
You sure about this?
Absolutely.
I know, I'm shredded.
And so humble, too!
What does this tattoo mean?
Uh...
it's for my twin sister.
Her name was Abigail.
Dray... I'm so sorry.
I don't... talk about her.
We don't have to.
No, no, it's fine.
I probably should.
We were eight.
At a...
at a neighbor's birthday party,
and it was before we adopted Josh, so...
it was just me and her.
And we were attached at the hip.
And then, it's like we
blinked, and she was gone.
She wandered off when no
one was looking, and...
that was the last time I saw her.
My parents were searching for
what felt like an eternity.
I mean, a couple people reported
a suspicious car in the
neighborhood, but...
no one knows.
Drayton... I'm so sorry.
I-I cannot even imagine
how hard that was for you.
On all of us. It... it was a nightmare.
And my dad...
He blames himself,
but it's not...
It's no one's fault.
But now, he puts all his
energy in me and the plan,
and if I stray even a little bit,
he freaks, and it's...
it's suffocating.
You know, I feel like Josh reminds him
of what family's supposed to be...
and, uh...
and I remind him of
losing his only daughter.
Your dad's just an
over-protective clownfish
who loves you.
Haven't you seen Finding Nemo?
Yeah.
Thanks for listening.
And if there's ever anything I can do...
Well, there is one thing.
Okay, my audition is
still a few weeks away,
so I'm-I'm working some things out.
Okay.
And if you don't like it...
please lie.
I'm gonna love it! All right?
Now, stop stalling and dance. Come on.
Drayton? Dinner's ready.
Dad, we'll be down in a minute.
No, dinner's ready now.
Dad, you're being so...
So what?
Downstairs, now.
Wait, don't go. I wanna
see your whole solo.
No, it's fine. Another time.
Look, I'm sorry my dad's such an asshole.
He's not.
He's concerned for you.
It comes from a good place.
And, besides, I told Nathan
I'd have dinner with him. Okay?
Okay.
Do you have a problem with Dallas?
The girl you got suspended
and ran off to California with
on my dime?
Yeah.
And I didn't just go for her.
I wanted to clear my head
and consider my options.
"Options"?
What options? You committed to Waco.
Boys, we're gonna need some plates.
I got it.
You know, you always just assumed
I wanted to go to there,
but there are other
schools with great teams.
Where is this coming from?
Waco has always been the plan.
Is this because of that girl?
Her name is Dallas!
She's a distraction.
Okay.
Drayton...
your father just wants what's best for you.
And, Leroy, Dallas is his girlfriend.
You need to give her a chance.
Now, I am going to invite her
to Dray's birthday party this weekend,
and we are all gonna be
on our best behavior.
Are you ready to face the wolves?
They love me.
Okay.
Smile!
Smiling.
Wow. You look amazing.
Aw... thanks!
But you're not my type.
Hi.
Yo, Coach!
I'm gonna find
literally any adult to talk to.
Thanks.
Ooh.
Thank you. My mom will love this.
It's a family recipe.
Technically, Nathan made it, but I watched.
Well, I can't wait to try it.
Dallas, I hear you're majoring in dance.
You cheerleaders are so fantastic
in the half-time shows.
Thank you.
Mom, Dallas is a
classically trained dancer.
That's impressive.
We would love to attend
your next performance.
That's so nice of you,
but I'm not sure when that'll be.
When you're at CalArts,
you'll have tons of recitals.
That's Dallas' top choice.
But it's very competitive.
But you're very talented.
Speaking of talent...
Cheers to the birthday boy.
You're looking at Waco's
next starting quarterback.
We're very, very proud.
Congrats, man.
Thank you.
You accepted, and you're starting?
That's huge!
Why didn't you tell me?
Nothing's official.
He's got a full ride.
All he's got to do is
sign on the dotted line.
Well, uh, I'm still waiting
to hear from a few places.
Alabama and, uh, Notre Dame
seem very interested, so...
I'm keeping an open mind.
An open mind to other schools?
Some in California, Georgia...
California? Son. No, I...
I'm not gonna let you follow
a girl across the country.
That is not your decision.
Can we just table this discussion?
No, no. I am not gonna let
you dismantle your future
and throw away this opportunity
over a high-school fling.
You don't know anything
about our relationship.
Look, Dallas is the best
thing to happen to me since...
Since what? The suspension? The parties?
You know damn well since what!
Since Abby.
I want a choice over my own life.
It's not just your life!
Yes, it fucking is!
Hey, enough!
Mom...
Um, I'm so sorry.
Thank you so much for having me.
Um, I have to go.
Dallas!
Am I the reason you
don't want to go to Waco?
Wow, somebody thinks highly of themself.
I'm serious.
Weren't you the one that
told me plans can change?
Yes.
Only if you want them to.
But don't make any big,
life-altering decisions
based on a relationship that's... you know?
No, I don't know.
That is not going anywhere!
I didn't realize we had an expiration date.
Yes, you did, because that is exactly why
I didn't want to date
you in the first place.
Okay, but you did.
We got together, and
now you're running away.
I am not running.
So what should we do, huh?
Since you can predict
exactly how everything's
supposed to play out,
like a dance routine...
what comes next?
I think we should break up.
Fine. Works for me.
We're closed.
You missed the last
three weeks of practice.
Emily's threatening to
kick you off the team.
Also wouldn't be shocked if
she had you assassinated.
Then let her.
I'm really busy right now.
I had to pick up some extra shifts at work.
I know you're sad and heartbroken,
and I want to help you get through this.
I'm fine!
And honestly, I don't even
know what you're doing here.
It's kinda dramatic.
Nuh-uh.
I am sick and tired of
your main-character energy.
Breakups are awful.
You know what else sucks?
A Princeton rejection.
Oh, Gabs.
Oh, no. When did...
I found out two weeks and,
like, six phone calls ago.
You know, I get you have baggage...
but it's not fair to push
away people who love you.
Mr. Douglas?
What's going on?
I thought you were at the studio.
I was. I'm sorry. I don't...
Are you okay?
I should... maybe go.
No, you-you don't have to.
I'll give you a call later.
Yeah.
Um, Dallas, whatever it is...
it'll be okay.
Okay.
Okay?
Yeah. Thank you. Thank you.
What's going on?
When did that happen?
You weren't the only one who
had fun at the away game.
Evidently.
Sit down. Let's talk.
Why is it
that the more you invest in something,
the more it lets you down?
Gabby hates me.
Our friendship's over. I'm
getting kicked off cheer.
And I'm not even gonna bother
sending in my audition video,
because I'm never getting in.
Like, everything is a mess.
Can I ask you a question, Dallas?
What do you love outside of dance?
You.
Besides your only living relative?
I don't know. Gabby?
Dallas.
You're as talented as Mom...
but she had so much
more than just dance.
She had us, friends, family...
things that made her life
so much more fulfilling.
What happened to Mom and Dad was tragic,
but it's the exception, not the rule.
Sometimes, the people you love stay.
When did you become so well-adjusted?
After therapy.
But you'll get there.
And you will audition
for CalArts in person.
You've worked too hard.
No, we can't afford it.
Actually, we can.
I've been saving up all year.
You're all set.
Aw...
Thank you.
Yeah, of course.
That's what brothers are for.
Take-out night.
Mom ordered your favorite.
Tell her thanks, but I'm not hungry.
Dray, when are you gonna
snap out of this, huh?
It's been weeks.
You're young.
All right?
I promise you...
there will be other girls.
This is not about Dallas.
Then what's it about?
About Waco?
No, Dad.
What?
It's about us.
We don't talk.
We talk all the time.
No.
You talk at me, but...
you don't listen.
You never even asked
me if I liked football,
or what I wanna do with my future,
or how I felt after...
After Abby.
Yeah.
Look, you expect me to live my life
for the both of us, but
that's just not possible.
Look, the main reason I went to California
was to visit with the head coaches
of USC and UCLA.
You did?
Yeah.
'Cause I love football
and I'm really good at it...
but I should be the one
to decide where I play.
There's no playbook for being a father.
I just want you to be happy.
All right? I'm sorry...
that I haven't made that clear.
Every moment of my life is
spent trying to make sure
you, your mom, and your
brother are okay, because...
because I couldn't do that for Abby.
Dad, it is not your fault that happened.
I love you, son.
I love you too.
Dallas Bryan?
Thank you.
Whenever you're ready.
"Bryan"?
Was your mother Rachel Bryan?
Yes.
We were roommates.
She was so talented.
She'd be very proud.
And, off the record...
we'd be lucky to have
you on campus next year.
Amazing!
You did it.
I'm sorry that I ghosted you,
and that I was so self-absorbed.
But mostly I'm sorry that I pushed you away
when you've always been
a great best friend.
A phenomenal best friend.
The most phenomenal!
And I love you more than
I could love any boy,
because you're my family.
You're forgiven.
Now tell me how your audition went.
It was amazing!
Yes! I knew it.
The faculty, they said they would, quote,
"be lucky to see me on campus,"
but I'm still waiting on
my official acceptance.
Congratulations.
We're absolutely killing it.
What about you?
I'm officially valedictorian.
And I got a summer internship
at the top law firm.
Princeton will rue the day!
Yeah, they will!
As I hang my Harvard degree
in my Supreme Court office.
Oh! Yes, ma'am!
How are things with Josh?
Honestly...
Things are great.
She accepted my prom-posal last night.
You know, I never thought
the word "prom" spelled out in pepperoni
would make me cry, but here we are.
I am so happy for you two.
I completely forgot about prom.
You could totally be
our beloved third wheel.
Unless...
Hey, babe.
No. No, I...
I think it's really over with Drayton.
But it's okay.
We're... we're graduating soon,
and I'll never have to see him again.
Is that what you want?
Gabs.
No, wait.
I said I'd stop meddling.
But he still talks about you all the time,
so do with that what you will.
All righty. Let's go.
Gabs, they're broken up. Just let it be.
Yeah, but you never know...
Hey.
Look, congrats on a great season.
Thanks. It was a team effort.
And we owe a lot to Coach.
I got into CalArts.
Never doubted you. Congrats, Cheer.
I know you didn't,
and to be honest,
you were the first person I wanted to tell.
Dallas, we can't keep doing this.
And I'm really proud of my solo...
which was definitely
inspired by our time together.
What do you mean?
I mean about living in the moment.
I guess I...
I really like who I am when I'm with you.
Are you trying to win me back?
No.
Yes!
Maybe.
I mostly wanted to apologize.
I got scared and I pushed you away
the minute things got serious,
and I don't know if it's
because I'm a Virgo...
or if it's because I'm
just seriously afraid
of losing someone I love again.
What did you just say?
I said, I love you, Drayton Lahey.
I love you too.
So what's next?
Let's just spend as much
time together as we can,
and I don't know what happens after...
but I'm okay with it.
Yes, sir.
Playing for you is an absolute dream.
Thank you.
You sure about this?
I want this to be your decision.
I'm sure.
Who knows...
maybe one day, we'll find
our way back to each other.
Okay! You sure that you got everything?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
Mm-hmm?
I double-checked your list. Right?
Which was your way of
double-checking my list.
That's the last of it.
I guess you're good to go.
Okay, this is... this is really happening.
Uh... I promise to visit.
I promise to call every day.
One... last thing.
Dad's recipe.
The council has deemed you worthy.
I'm gonna miss you, kid.
Me too.
Ready to go?
Don't want you to miss your flight.
Yeah.
See ya, Coach.
I'll pick up the rest.
Yep.
Bye.
Heads up!
Nice catch, Cheer.
Not my name, Quarterback!
What are you doing here?
You're looking at USC's
new starting quarterback.
Why didn't you tell me?
What's the fun in that?
When you were touring,
I visited with the head
coaches of USC and UCLA.
Ultimately... USC was the pick.
What did your dad say?
It was tough. You know?
But we worked through a lot,
and in the end, he was totally supportive.
Dray, I am so happy for you.
I can't believe you held
onto this for so long.
Oh, trust me, it took everything in me
not to ruin the surprise.
Was it worth it?
Absolutely.
Is this real?
This is very real.